It's always deadliest before the dawn.
Zeros and Ones is a war, thriller film directed by Abel Ferrara.
Called to Rome to stop an imminent terrorist bombing, a soldier desperately seeks news of
his imprisoned brother — a rebel with knowledge that could thwart the attack.
Navigating the capital's darkened streets, he races to a series of ominous
encounters to keep the Vatican from being blown to bits.
JJ / Justin, played by Ethan Hawke.
Laughing Russian Agent, played by Cristina Chiriac.
Phil, played by Phil Neilson.
Luciano, played by Valerio Mastandrea.
Valeria, played by Valeria Correale.
Serious Russian Agent, played by Dounia Sichov.
Zeros and Ones is a 2021 thriller film written and directed by Abel Ferrara.
Starring Ethan Hawke, it follows an American mercenary attempting to uncover a
plot to blow up the Vatican during the COVID-19 lockdowns in Rome.
The film had its world premiere in the main competition of the 74th Locarno Film
Festival in August 12, 2021, where it won the Best Direction Award.
It received a limited theatrical release and a simultaneous digital
release on the United States by Lionsgate on November 19, 2021.
The film explores themes of rome, italy, twin brother, terrorism, pandemic.
The tone is dark and intense.